winona@winonaso.com www.winonaso.com www.winsemporium.etsy.com



hello

I'm a graphic designer who strives to create the perfect balance of beauty and clairity in design.

I have experience in both print and digital design ranging from presentations, reports, bids, social media graphics, exhibition design, and trade shows.

Toronto, ON

education

MASTER OF DIGITAL MEDIA, Ryerson University September 2016 - August 2017

Masters Thesis - AvatarMe: Digital Avatars in a Theme Park Queue Creating a Better Experience and an Emotional Connection

Graduate Assistant for Creativity and Collaboration (CRI 810), Teaching Assistant for Digital Skills and Innovation for the Global Economy (EID 100)

Ryerson Graduate Fellowship Scholarship

BACHELOR OF ARTS, University of Waterloo September 2010 - December 2014

Major in Honours English - Rhetoric & Professional Writing, specializing in Digital Arts Communication

Arts & Business Co-op Program

UW Merit Scholarship, 2014-2015 - Rhetoric and Digital Design Award

passions

PERSONAL ETSY STORE

www.winsemporium.etsy.com I am the creator and designer of Wins Emporium that sells hand-made cross stitch patterns, designs, and buttons.

UNIT GUIDER, 68th Toronto Guides

Currently serving as 68th Toronto Guides Unit Treasurer and Guider

Spent 10 years as a girl member with 8th Vancouver Girl Guides

Received Chief Commisioner's Award and Richard C.C. Tse Outstanding Guiding and Scouting Award

BOARD GAMER

Primarily plays Eurogames and solo games.

Graphic Designer for LionWing's Gun and Gun.

Proofreader for LionWing's Gun and Gun, LionWing's Kradia Wild Hunt Festival, and Funtail's Glen More II: Chronicles.

work experience

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER, Tulip

November 2018 - Present

Responsible for executing creative concepts, design, production of brand assets for both print and web for marketing campaigns

Design and create RFPs in order to win contracts from external companies

Work with external agencies in organizing and design of booth, signage, collateral, and advertising for events and trade shows

PROGRAM COORDINATOR, University of Toronto September 2018 - Present

Manage and assist the Technology Leadership Initiative program by running industry events, workshops, and site visits

Provide general administration support to professors and executives leading the program

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, Lord Cultural Resources October 2017 - June 2018

Create PowerPoint and Word templates for presentations, reports, and bids in order to win contracts from potential clients

Design large scale graphics for museum exhibitions, as well as displays, handouts and pamphlets for conferences

Implement and code web pages for the company website ensuring visual consistency and appeal

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER, Munaluchi Bridal January 2016 - December 2016

Designed and created assets for various social media outlets

Created posters, postcard invitations, and digital badges for bridal conventions and events

DIGITAL PRODUCTION ASSISTANT, Centre for Extended Learning April 2015 - April 2016

Develop lecture slides and materials for University of Waterloo online courses

Collaborated with professors, other production assistants, developers in designing and publishing course content

Created illustrations and icons for information graphics, and diagrams in online courses with Adobe Illustrator